エルさんが
Kimi iro ni Somaru
君色に染まっちゃう
"Dyed With Your Color"
「Music」
DECO*27
「Motion」
「Choreo」
つん
足太ぺんた
「MME」
「Models」
rui、化身バレッタ
落書きさん、公開
怪獣対若大将P
ゆづき、@Ai
「Camera
& Video」
remidapyon
期待してすぐに諦めて
I got my hopes up, just to talk myself down
曖昧な答えに流されては
You're stringing me along with vague answers
自分だけ置いて行かれるような
It's almost like I'm being left behind
そんなイメージが胸をつつく夜だ
and that thought pains me at night
覚えてるような　覚えていないような
I can almost remember, but not quite
憧れと記憶を彷徨うよ
I'm meandering through precious memories
僕は君のために　君は僕のために
Wouldn't it be wonderful
生まれたならちょっと嬉しいね
If we were born for each other?
気付いたら君色に染まってるような
Before I knew it, I was dyed with your color
何気ない言葉で汚して欲しい
I want you to stain me with those fleeting words of yours
ずっとわからないフリを続けてきたんだ
I've always put up a facade of innocence
この時が来るまで
Anticipating this very moment
もしかして、君と釣り合ってないかな？
Could it be that we weren't meant for each other?
そんな不安もたまに過るけれど
I can't say I've never had those thoughts
いつも困らせてばかりでごめんね
I'm sorry I've always gotten in your way
ああ、好きだよ、好きだよ、好きだよって伝えたい
But I just wanted to say I love you
傷付けないように言葉を探しても
Even if I choose my words to not hurt you
空回り、気持ちに急かされて
I rush in with half-complete thoughts
ねぇ間違ってるような これで合ってるような
It's like we're both right and wrong
二人の答え、ずっとよろしくね
I'll leave to you to decide both our fates
気付いたら君色に染まってるような
Before I knew it, I was dyed with your color
何気ない言葉で汚して欲しい
I want you to stain me with those fleeting words of yours
ずっとわからないフリを続けてきたんだ
I've always put up a facade of innocence
この時が来るまで
Anticipating this very moment
もしかして、君と釣り合ってないかな？
Could it be that we weren't meant for each other?
そんな不安もたまに過るけれど
I can't say I've never had those thoughts
いつも困らせてばかりでごめんね
I'm sorry I've always gotten in your way
好
き
だ
よ
ああ、
よって伝えたい
But I just wanted to say I love you
好
き
だ
よ
好
き
だ
よ
ああ、好きだよ、好きだよ、好きだよって伝えたい
But I just wanted to say I love you